ppcsecure.com 2015-11-21

# Privacy Policy | PPCSecure

## PPCSecure Privacy Policy

_Last modified on July 29, 2015_

### Privacy policy for PPCSecure clients using our services to track data on their websites

#### Information collection and usage

PPCSecure is the sole owner of any data collected on our websites. We will not sell, rent or share your personal information with any outside source for any purpose outside of the purposes which may be included in this privacy policy.

#### Usernames, Passwords, Security, and Billing data safeguarded

Any information we collect while you are using our websites or services and any personal data we collect about you that is of sensitive nature, including usernames, passwords, security questions and answers and billing information is considered confidential. This data is secured on owned or leased servers in a private facility that is guarded by physical security and virtual security measures. Your data is also protected by use of a username and password. You should keep your password and user name confidential and never share these with anybody. We also train our internal staff and any contractors who work with us on the proper handling of sensitive customer information. Failure to abide by our privacy standards is grounds for termination of employment with PPCSecure. We take your privacy very seriously.

#### Sign up and Billing Information 

While registering for the services we may offer, you may be asked for personal information such as credit card numbers, addresses or your name. Any information collected via these forms on our websites is transmitted to us via an SSL encrypted connection to ensure the safety of your information. We limit physical and virtual access to the servers which store this information in order to protect your information.

PPCSecure uses an outside secure solution to process our credit card transactions for goods and services. We have ensured through our own auditing procedures that these companies do everything within their power to protect and securely transmit your data during any transaction.

#### Other Ways We May Use Your Information

In addition to the uses for the information listed above, we may also use personal information that you submit to us for the following reasons:

-To contact you when necessary for additional information that is required to complete or fulfill your order; determine if you are satisfied with our services; survey you to gather information used to improve our products, inform you that an upgrade of your services is available; or to inform you regarding the billing or technical status of your subscription.

-To contact you with information or special offers about PPCSecure's products and services.

We may also, from time-to-time, share your basic contact information with affiliates, third parties, or business partners, who may then use that information to contact you with special offers, promotions, or to inform you about their products and services.

PPCSecure may also be forced to release personal or account related information to comply with law enforcement, judicial proceedings, or legal matters, to enforce the terms of any of our user agreements, or to protect the rights, property or safety of PPCSecure, our staff, our clients, or others.

#### Use of Cookies and Session-Tracking

PPCSecure uses cookies to track data regarding the use of our websites and services. These cookies do not ever contain any private personally identifiable data such as your name, age, address, or email address. We also use tracking cookies to make access to certain parts of our websites easier and more efficient for you.

We also may collect other data such as IP address, time of visit and store user preferences in session data or in a cookie to make navigating our websites more efficient for you.

#### Third-Party and Linked Websites

This privacy policy only pertains to this website and any other website owned by PPCSecure. We do not endorse and are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third-party, regardless of their affiliation with PPCSecure. This includes other websites which we may link to or refer your to for outside services. 

#### Business Transition

In the event that PPCSecure is sold to, acquired, or merged with another company, your information and account data will likely be amongst the transferred assets. You will be notified via email within 14 days of such a transaction taking place and we will also post notice of such on the homepage of this website.

#### Modifications to This Privacy Policy

If PPCSecure makes any changes to the way we use your personally identifiable information, we will update this page. We may do so without notice or prior warning. You should check this page every time you visit our website to ensure you are always aware of our current privacy policy.

### Privacy policy for Visitors to Websites using PPCSecure to track data

#### Purpose of this privacy policy

PPCSecure has created this privacy policy to specifically outline what kind of data we collect, how that data is used, and what measures we use to protect and control access to your information.

#### Personal data is not collected or stored 

PPCSecure does not collect or store any type of personal contact information from the visitors to our client's web pages. Visiting a website with our software installed or services in use will not result in the collection of names, phone numbers, mailing addresses, e-mail addresses or any other type of personal data.

#### Collection of end-user data

If you are a visitor to any client's website using the services of PPCSecure, or you click on one of our client's internet advertisment links, you should fully expect that the following data will be collected and stored: Your IP address, browser type, general geographic location, unique user ID tag generated by a cookie installed on your computer, time of your visit, and the referring webpage or referring search engine, along with whichever keywords you used to find the client's website.

#### How your data is stored

The data collected from your visit to a client's website using PPCSecure's services may be stored at a central server owned or leased by PPCSecure. The data may be stored for a period of up to ten (10) years. The server is located in a secure facility and is protected by strong passwords and physical protection.

#### How your data is used

PPCSecure's purpose in collecting your usage data is to clearly identify repeat visitors from the same source in an effort to prevent malicious use of our client's pay-per-click advertisements. No third party other than the specific PPCSecure client or PPCSecure staff will be provided access to your data at any time. Some or all usage data may also be used to create reports which will then be submitted to search engines to obtain a refund or recompense for the PPCSecure client.

#### Use of Cookies

It is the policy of PPCSecure to use cookies only in an effort to identify repeat visitors from certain PPC Search Engines. The cookie never collects or includes personal data such as the visitor's name, phone number, e-mail address or physical address. It may, however, include unique computer-based information used to positively identify a specific computer on the internet.

PPCSecure also uses tracking code on our servers to track anonymous information about visitors' activity. This code contacts PPCSecure's servers, receives a response, and submits information to PPCSecure about the visit.

#### Modifications to This Privacy Policy

If PPCSecure makes any changes to the way we use your personally identifiable information, we will update this page. We may do so without notice or prior warning. You should check this page every time you visit our website to ensure you are always aware of our current privacy policy.
